top26.net 2011-12-12

# Privacy Policy - Top 26 Gaming

there are currently 618 visitors online!

Welcome to the Top 26 Gaming sites, providing the best free gaming and emulation links **since 2001**. You should bookmark this site now, as we always have the newest and best gaming sites, updated daily! We do not allow any sites which have force voting or excessive popup's, so where ever you click you will always get a quality link! Looing for funny videos? You can watch the latest [funny videos](http://www.viduu.com/ "Funny Videos") and funny video clips at [Viduu](http://www.viduu.com/ "Funny Video Clips"). 

Sites with  icon are particularly high quality - Votes in are reset **every day** at 5am GMT.

**Privacy Policy**

Top 26 Gaming does not sell, rent, or give out any information about our visitors. This includes email addresses, IP addresses, or any other type of information we might collect. 

Top 26 Gaming does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. 

Top 26 Gaming currently collects information about browser types, operating systems, screen resolution, screen colors, and other information which we can use to help design our web sites. These are basic computer stats which can only be used to make a small demographic of the types of computers people have. 

Top 26 Gaming is not responsible for anything on its affiliates websites. The sites linked to by Top 26 Gaming are developed by people over whom Top 26 Gaming exercises no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. We recommend going to the affiliates website for information on their privacy policy. 

All question about Top 26 Gaming's privacy statement should be e-mailed to: webmaster@top26.net. Feel free to contact us any time and we'll answer any additional questions you may have.
